Farha Qureshi

Sr. Software Developer

6+ years of IT experience with .Net Technology

farha12.bhopal@gmail.com

+91-9174147816

70/1, Green Park Colony, Indore, India Q

http://linkedin.com/in/farha-qureshi-640438105 in

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. Software Engg at Infobeans Indore - 05/2022 to Present

Net Developer at Swastika Investmart Indore - 09/2019 to 05/2022

Programmer at NIC Bhopal - 09/2016 to 01/2019 & 05/2019 to 07/2019

Profile Skills:

- Application: Web based, Window Based, Console
- Application, Web services, Web APIs, Three tier
- architecture, MVC
- Databases: SQL Server, MySql, Cosmos DB
- Programming Language: C#

Tools: Visual Studio 2022, Postman, Swagger, Zoho, Jeera, SVN,

GIT, TFS, Worked on SSRS. Also worked on Jquery & MVC.

EDUCATION

B.E-CSE: 8.55 CGPA Higher Secondary XII: 57.8 % High School X: 7.2 CGPA

Professional Projects

Project I: eUparjaneUparjan Software is a web based application. It is a Computerization of Food grain Procurement System Of Madhya Pradesh. Main purpose of this software is to give easy solution to farmers to sell their crop to government and get end to end payment without any malpractices.

(http://mpeuparjan.nic.in/mpeuparjan/ Home.aspx/)

Project II: Public Distribution System Software is a web based application for Allotment of food grain ,allotment has to be done every month so in this software Fair price shop wise allotment record can be monitored by the officials with separate logins

(http://mpsc.mp.nic.in/pdsallot/default.aspx)

Project |||: EKYC eKYC software contain whole KYC process including Digital signing, Aadhar authentication, PAN verification, Bank Verification https://swastika.co.in

Project IV: **Webware** It is a web based ecommerce application having 3 layer architecture. Managing client based multiple websites in a single project. https://partsking.ca

Project V: **Legal Forms** It is a Survey application designed on .Net Core 6.0 Web Apis & Entity framework.

SKILLS



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Coding and applying logic related to the development tasks, writing the front-end code and handling it from the back end as well, Web Site, Window based applications

Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability and testing the code according to scenarios

Designed SSRS, applying logics in SQL, applying formulas, conditional suppressing, and using stored2 procedures and views.

SQL Server Database Design, Database Maintenance, Developing SQL Queries, Stored Procedures, Views and Triggers

Working with senior developers to manage large, complex design projects for MP government.

Worked with Third Party Services like Digital esigning, Aadhar authentication, PAN verification, Bank Verification

Designed and developed window based aplications. Created console base schedulers for sending Email and SMS

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

HIndi

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Art & Craft Dress Designing